Yui, you're still not up?
Still not feeling well?
Want to stay home again today?
Oh, Yaegashi!
Decided to be a little more
fashionably late than usual?
Sure, I guess.
You won't believe what you missed!
Your favorite girl was doing
something you would've liked to see.
Man, that was genius!
My favorite girl?
You know, the one in your club.
You mean Nagase?
Oh? So Nagase's the one you're after?
I didn't say that!
But the only CRC members in our class are you, Inaba, and Nagase.
And Nagase was the first thing that popped
into your head when I said "your favorite girl."
You sneak!
Watase!
We've got a meeting
in the Soccer Club room! Come on!
Great.
There goes my lunch break.
Well, tell me if you ever need any help winning her over.
I'll be sure to lend you a hand! Later!
W-Wait!
Something I would've liked?
Taichi.
Why are you late?
Did something happen?
Yeah.
I think my desires got—
Not so loud, retard!
Couldn't you tell me
that without hurting me?
Maybe if you weren't so retarded.
I've never gotten violent without a reason.
You sure about that?
Hm?
Nothing, sorry.
So what desire got unleashed?
I think it was...
a desire for sleep.
What?
Ow!
You made me worry over
you just wanting more sleep?
It was horrible!
Well, I was asleep, so I don't remember, but...
Onii-chan, wake up!
You're going to be late!
Come on, wake up!
Onii-chan? Onii-chan?!
Onii-chan!
Wake up, Onii-chan!
...my mom managed to calm her
down and send her off to school.
My mom told me
everything after I woke up.
They didn't call an ambulance?
They probably would've
if I hadn't woken up.
I have to apologize to my sister later.
I texted her, but I need to get her ice cream or—
Shut it, siscon!
It's normal for a brother to love his sister!
Couldn't have been anything
other than an unleashed desire
if you were sleeping that heavily.
Your desires were unleashed while you were asleep,
forcing you to act on your
desire to sleep a little more.
As long as we're on the topic...
Just curious, but was Nagase hit by a desire for sleep, too?
You heard the man.
Hey, Taichi...
Don't you ever feel like breaking the silence when everyone's all quiet or when things get serious?
No, not really.
Wait, you didn't...
This morning, we had a quiz, so it was dead silent.
Suddenly I felt like shouting...
Yahoo!
Yahoo...
They believed me when I said I was daydreaming.
The whole class laughed their heads off.
The general reaction was pretty much, "Sounds like something Iori'd do."
I couldn't believe it!
I suddenly stand up and shout, "Yahoo!" and all I get is a "Oh, that's so like her"?
What kind of person do they think I am?!
So you're the kind of person who likes to shout stuff like "Yahoo!" in class.
You could act a little more surprised!
Man, you two have some pretty mild desires.
So Yui was absent again today?
I told her about Balloon Vine already,
and that we all need to meet to discuss this.
I called her earlier and asked if we could go visit, but...
You don't need to come.
I'll be back in school by next week.
They'll probably stop talking
about yesterday by then.
Yui...
Dammit!
It's all Balloon Vine's fault.
Pulling stuff like this again...
If he makes Yui cry again...
I'll kill him.
Aoki! Name five good things about Kiriyama Yui!
She's cute! She's cheerful!
She's strong! She's super cute!
Her hair's pretty!
She's tiny! She's pure!
She's childish, but in a good way...
Five isn't enough at all!
You didn't need to say "cute" twice.
So, have you cooled off a bit?
Don't let yourself get too worked up.
If we don't think of anything crazy,
our unleashed desires won't be crazy either.
You're right.
My bad.
Yeah.
As long as it's something like shouting "Yahoo!"
we can look back on it and laugh.
Hey, Taichi! Are you picking on me?
Are you?!
So if we get frustrated or angry, we can calm ourselves by just thinking of Yui.
Well, in your case, anyway.
I'm really worried about Yui.
Beating the crap out of those boys might be really traumatic for her.
I have to save her.
I'll go talk to her.
What? Taichi?
Crap!
His desire got unleashed!
Taichi, wait!
Wait!
Snap out of it, Taichi!
I have to save her!
I have to save Kiriyama!
Just how badly do you want to save people?
You're creeping me out.
Let go of me! Let go of me!
Snap out of it, Taichi!
Calm down!
Iori!
Tackle him from the front!
You got it!
Wait, why me?!
If you want brute force, ask Aoki!
No. If we can get Taichi to experience a stronger desire for something else,
we might be able to change his
impulse or end the whole episode.
You really think that'll work?
No shame in trying.
Now get under him and
fan the flames of Taichi's lust.
No! No!
Well, I don't mind giving it a try, but...
Iori-chan! Do it for Taichi! Please!
Could you guys stop screwing around already?!
Is there a problem?
You didn't look very intimidating.
It was just you being a selfless freak and trying to save someone again.
Hey, did it end?
Huh?
Uh...
Yeah.
It doesn't look like our desires get unleashed for very long.
If you can't act on them right away,
they might just end without anything happening.
But isn't whatever incites our desires being unleashed usually right in front of us?
You're probably most focused on the stuff around you.
You actually made a valid point for once!
Why is that such a surprise?!
I have my moments, too!
What does Balloon Vine want this time?
Just like with personality switching,
he probably just wants to observe us and see if anything interesting happens.
He just wants to make waves between us.
Don't look at me with those lewd eyes of yours.
My eyes aren't lewd!
Wait. My eyes don't always look lewd, do they?
You really might be the one in the most danger this time.
What do you mean?
Back at the hospital, you were
completely serious about dying for Iori.
Who knows what'll happen if a desire like that got unleashed.
You...
might really die this time.
I went to Class 1-1, and they told me Yui's absent again.
She said that she was okay when I called her last night...
I just hope she hasn't lost it.
Lost it? What's that supposed to mean?
Just like with personality switching,
we don't know if someone will break down over this.
We definitely have to visit Yui today.
Yeah.
Quit looking so grim.
If we go there looking like that,
we might actually make it worse for Yui.
Hello?
Kiriyama-san! Come out to play!
What?
Wait, Iori?
What're you...
Just so you know, I'm here, too!
And Inaba-chan and Taichi.
It doesn't have a camera.
You're all here?
Yeah. The whole CRC.
We're here to visit you. Mind if we come in?
Is there anyone else home right now?
It's only me right now.
But no.
Don't come in. Go home.
Even if we don't let the guys in?
How about just Inaban and me?
That's not the problem. Just—
Oh my.
Are you Yui's friends?
Come on, Yui.
Open the door.
Your friends came all this way.
Tell them to go home.
I'm really sorry.
She locked herself in her room
and refuses to come out.
Don't worry about it, Mom.
I think she's just a bit shook up right now.
She'll be back to normal in no time.
That's right, Mother!
Just leave it to us!
You're such reliable friends.
Thank you so much.
Don't mention it.
Tell me if you need anything.
Yui, you shouldn't make
your mom worry like this.
Why don't we talk face-to-face, just once?
It's pretty hard on all of us right now.
Just go home.
I'm really happy that
you're thinking about me.
I'll go back to school soon.
I didn't want to do this.
What are you going to do?
Nothing really.
I'm just going to open the
door with some magic words.
Who the heck are you?
I will now be revealing
Kiriyama Yui's deepest secrets.
First, her three sizes are, from the top, A—
Stop! Stop! Stop!
I'll let you in, so please, stop!
It would've been so much fun if I got to say that.
Inaban, you're scaring me.
Sorry for coming uninvited.
But...
No, it's okay.
It's my fault.
Are you feeling well?
If not, we can go home now.
There's a huge zit on your forehead—
No! No! No! Don't look!
I made a huge mistake!
Been eating your heart out or something?
N-No!
I suddenly had a craving to eat a lot of sweet stuff yesterday.
I felt like dying when I counted all the calories!
That's just scary.
Your desires were unleashed when you were hungry.
You aren't staying home from
school because of that zit, are you?
Of course I wouldn't do that!
Then Balloon Vine unleashing
your desires has to be the cause.
Don't be silly.
We're all in the same boat.
But...
I don't want to hurt anyone.
When those boys started to get rough with those girls,
I thought I had to save them.
And then I went out of control.
Balloon Vine is to blame for that.
But I really thought about beating them to a pulp.
I just can't deal with men.
Who knows what I'll do if it happens again?
I can't go outside like this!
Quit playing the victim.
Inaban?
Don't shut yourself in and leave the rest of us for dead.
But no one will get hurt as long as I don't see them.
Do you understand the situation?
I don't think you do.
Hey, Inaba...
"Nothing will happen if no one's around."
Yeah. I thought so, too.
But will Balloon Vine think that's interesting?
He wants to see us do something interesting.
If we don't do what he wants, he'll force us to.
He'll make someone jump off a bridge again, or maybe something even worse!
We might all end up in the hospital!
Do you know what kind of problems you could be causing us by taking the easy way out?!
Do you?!
I don't know anymore!
What should I—
Quit bawling!
You think crying's going to help?!
Inaban!
Sorry, Yui.
I didn't mean to go that far.
My desires were unleashed, and I couldn't stop.
But that's what you really thought, right?
You think I'd know?! Don't ask me!
Huh?
All I did was ask if you know how Kiriyama's doing.
I want to know that, too!
You don't have to yell at me!
No, that's not...
I didn't mean to yell—
You think you're better than me just because you've got a cute face?
I don't...
Hey. Not going to help her out?
Stop right there.
I'm sorry, Setouchi-san.
Kiriyama-san is a bit of a
delicate issue for her right now.
And with everyone asking her about Kiriyama-san,
she ran out of patience.
Isn't that right, Nagase-san?
Uh, yeah.
I'm worried about her, too, so...
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
You don't need to apologize like that.
I said something that I shouldn't have.
I'm sorry, too.
Man, Fujishima-san's so cool!
Inaba...
Inaba.
I'm going straight home today.
Later.
Inaba, what do you mean?
Do you have to do something?
Not really.
"Not really"?
Kiriyama hasn't come back to school yet.
So?
Shouldn't we visit Kiriyama today, too?
I'd just make things worse if I went.
Is that why you didn't do anything when Nagase yelled?
Everything would go to hell in a handbasket if I got involved.
So I'm not going to the club room either.
But Kiriyama's suffering.
I know you feel bad about what happened yesterday, but—
Like hell that's a reason.
Don't give up like that!
We still have to do something about it!
Don't think that everyone is like you, putting others before themselves.
There are times when my hands are full.
That's not a reason to abandon
someone when they're suffering!
Quit trying to force your creepy, dumbass ideals on me!
You've let me down, Inaba.
I never thought you'd turn your back on a friend.
I never thought you were that kind of person.
Sorry I'm that kind of person.
These things have the worst timing.
For Inaban, Taichi, and me.
I keep calling Inaba, but she won't answer.
I'm going to apologize as soon as I see her tomorrow.
Right!
We need to apologize quick when stuff like this happens. It's just water under the bridge.
I'm sure Inaba-chan knows that it's not really your fault, too.
Okay!
It's just the three of us heading over to Yui's today!
Yeah!
I'm sure Yui's feeling a bit better now—
I said to stop it, you two!
We're doing it my way this time.
You're just a selfish freak that can't stand seeing Yui sad!
It feels so... empty.
Well, you couldn't help yourself.
I think people hurting each other is inevitable.